## Jonathan Hall

# Raleigh, NC 27603 jchall1217@msn.com www.linkedin.com/in/jonathan-hall-jch47

## **Professional Summary**

Motivated, dependable, and curious professional with 8 years of experience in customer service, management, leadership, and creative output in the culinary field and 3 years of similar experience in the health/wellness field. Currently pursuing a degree in Computer Programming and Web Development and looking to transition to a career in technology.

## Education

Wake Tech Community College: Raleigh, NC

Associates of Applied Sciences in Computer Programming/Web Development

August 2020-Present

Current GPA: 3.7

Asheville School of Massage and Yoga: Asheville, NC

Licensed Massage and Body Work Therapist

October 2017-March 2018

## **Professional Experience**

#### CommerceCX, Cary, NC

Associate Full-Stack Developer

July 2022-Present

- O Studying and working with the SalesForce platform to help with integration services
- O Working as a member of the product development team on a stand-alone business web application
- O Designing and developing responsive web pages for company pages, integrating SalesForce web to lead forms and executing SEO practices

#### Barcelona Wine Bar, Raleigh, NC

November 2020-July 2022

Sauté Cook/Prep Cook/Shift Leader

- O Preparing and creating Sauté entrees and small plate Spanish tapas
- O As a crew leader in the kitchen, manage, train, and assist new employees
- O Demonstrate effective communication and mental flexibility while managing own responsibilities and monitoring/coordinating the rest of the kitchen

## Modern Market Eatery, Boulder, CO

December 2018-April 2020

Cook/Prep Cook/Shift Leader/Customer Service

- O Preparing and creating healthy, made from scratch dishes, and organizing/executing large catering orders.
- O As a versatile employee in the kitchen and front of the house, overseeing the line, training new employees, managing shift responsibilities, and attending to customer needs and inquiries
- O Demonstrate leadership and communication skills to focus and motivate team towards a common goal. Reliability and adaptability to remain calm and organized during high-volume pressure.

## **Related Experience**

- Wake Tech Programming Club
- Codecademy Front-End Engineer/HTML/CSS/JavaScript Courses
- IBM Blockchain Essentials
- Excel with Dell Mentorship Program 2022